Ready? Seino! Nacchi-koto!
One more time.
Ready! Nacchikoto!
Rinomaru making start!
It's like our making of.
It's the shooting of Candy 2 Hanamaru music video.
Here we go.
Yes, my name is Murakawa Mibe Aya. I'm Mibe Murakawa, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
Well, I'm a little nervous.
I woke up at 5:30 in the morning, and it's been cold, and I've been having trouble with the members and the governor.
I'm Satono Fukuyama, a.k.a. "Yes, I'm Satono Fukuyama, a.k.a. Norimaru, and I'm going to try my best to stand up straight as if I'm far away.
I'm really looking forward to the weather, and I'm sure it's going to be very cold, so I'm going to be wearing a lot of clothes.
I'm sure it's going to be a cold day, so I'm going to try my best not to say "it's cold".
This is Nanako Ogawa from Candy in the middle, and this is our first mv shoot as Candy in the middle.
I can't open my eyes because it's too bright today, but I'll try to cover it up by smiling.
I'll do my best, Bibi!
It's my first music video as Candy Tune and I'm really looking forward to it, but it's so cold and everyone has gathered here from early in the morning,
I'm really looking forward to this first music video as Candy Tune, but it's so cold and everyone has gathered here from early in the morning.
I will do my best today to deliver something good to you all.
My name is Minami-Natsu.
I've been practicing in the mirror ever since the shooting was decided and the storyboards and stuff came in.
I'll do my best to show that a little bit.
This song is like a great support song.
I'm going to do my best to make this music video so that it will cheer people up whenever they see it. I like to cut off Kiri from Candytoon.
It's cold, it's cold, but I'm going to do my best, and I'm going to make a face that everyone will like.
I want to do my best.
Okay, I'll do my best for the photo shoot.
It's cold and today is the first music video for CHANDYTUNE, so I'm full of energy.
I'm really looking forward to it, and I'm having my hair done in a really cute way, and I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm going to do my best now. You've got my support!
Thanks. I'll do my best.
Delicious! Delicious! I'm a bird eater in every making.
I mean, how dry is this stuff?
Pause.
It's so cute!
What do we have here? Oh, put it in, put it in, put it in!
Oh, it's hot!
Pace to come in a bag
We'll get some protein.
Salad!
Tarako pasta!
Yakiniku... am I having it today?
Why?
I'm sleepy.
Why are you eating today? Because I'm sleepy.
Let's go eat cod roe pasta.
Let's go.
You eat it every time?
I want to.
I do.
It's just...
You're picking on him, aren't you?
Shar-Pei, Shar-Pei.
There are girls like that.
Like in dramas.
Drama.
Like, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama, drama...
I thought you were a rock! Here you are!
I'm the most bullied girl in my class... and the most expensive flower in my class.
That one's cute too
Classmates are so cute!
It's no surprise...
I'm cute, right?
You're so cute!
You look cute today, shrimp.
So cute!
You're really cute!
You're really cute.
Really cute.
The girls from the school next door
Rumor has it
Surely a girl who will be the talk of the town
I'm a heroine
Yeah, she just transferred to a new school.
She's too cute
But she's so sweet
She's like a good girl.
Hello
He's so cute.
So cute
Relax.
Thank you.
Very beautiful.
So pretty.
Wow.
They're so cute.
They're cute shoes, aren't they?
Cute shoes.
I want to take a picture of this cute little girl, Lee.
I want to take a picture of these.
Shi-chan!
Shi-chan.
Let's do something like this.
I'm looking forward to it.
Shi-chan over here.
Wow.
He's so cute!
I thought it was going to be a cakewalk, but now...Now that I thought it was going to be kakukyu
Oh no!
Cute!
It's cute.
Can I?
Oh, my God! She's so cute!
Is it a baby? Not yet.
Little Happy.
Gruesome! Too much!
Is it a Shiba Inu?
Mamejima
So cute! Hey, where's Nachiko?
Where's Nachiko?
Nachiko!
She's cute!
Shut up!
Rainbow Bridge.
Are you Blue Suites?
No!
I just taught him the best jumps.
Rainbow Bridge?
No!
Like the Nihombashi.
Japan Bridge.
It leads to the Sky Tree.
It leads to the ribbon people.
Kiri's been very naughty lately.
Good morning, everyone!
We're Candidu.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
Good morning.
It's cold
Oh my God, it's glowing. It's so bad.
I don't know how many I gave you.
Take one.
Who's got one?
One?
Seriously, do you really remember the cheerleading squad? All these guys are my menkara, all these guys are my menkara, all these guys are my menkara, all these guys are my menkara, all these guys are my menkara, all these guys are my menkara, all these guys are my menkara
Because they're my menkara, they're all my menkara, they're all my menkara, they're all my menkara
all these men are my menkara all these men are my menkara all these men are my menkara
Because of my menkara, these menkara
Because they are my menkara, they are my menkara
This menkara because of my menkara
Because of my Menkara, this Menkara
This menkara because it's my menkara, this menkara because it's my menkara, and these mazes are all mine, and these mazes are all mine.
But all these straws, all these swimsuit menkas, all these mais, all these mais, all these mais, all these mais, all these mais
I can't open my eyes because I'm too dazzled, don't look at me.
I'm okay with saying "negaman." I like it, too, Chip. Mr. Carr... One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Oh, my God!
That's great!
I'm so empty, I can't hear you.
This world is so green.
Eh, I know.
It's so dark.
The world is green.
Wait, once I turn that way, I can't do it anymore. It's over. Please go with the feeling that you should look at me. Yes, I will. Thank you. Yes.
What?
It's started.
Yes.
Please.
Yes, please. Yes, please. Yes, please. Yes, please. Please.
One, two, one, two, three.
Now, you know, the middle of the bridge is supposed to be the center, and it feels really good when it's there.
So may I ask you to do the same thing one more time?
As many times as you want! It's great! Yes!
It felt so good when you went in there.
So cute!
We are! Thank you!
I'm Sandy Tun.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
How's it going? I just finished my first cut.
I don't know...
I don't know.
But I think I did what I practiced.
Kanamaru
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow! You're so smart!
My bangs got too short, even though I didn't cut them, so I'm having them stopped.
Can I do it again?
Yes! Ready!
Cute! This is a good balance.
I'm going to go to Japan...
Who's cute?
He's a good guy!
I knew it!
I can do it! I can do it!
What? I'm not good at this.
And I'm not even good at it,Moreover,
And it's a little scary because it's top butter.
I don't know what to do. I haven't even thought about what I'm going to do.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Is this one shot?
I'm not doing mine.
Thank you for the cut.
That's a little much for one moment, but I'll give you one more because it's cute, one more because it's cute.
Thank you, sir, but thank you again. I don't know if I did it right.
It was fun.
I'm embarrassed about the lip scene.
I do weird things.
It makes it awkward.
Music
Thank you very much.
Maybe I've got a little bit of soul in me.
Polka dots are delicious.
But it's fun. You give me great compliments.
Compliments!
It's amazing, it's kind of motivating.
I feel like I'm getting prettier.
Oh, well.
You're so dazzling!
I love it, it's perfect! It was super cute! Boy and girl, Maho, the letter and the picture catch in the ball of sunshine
So cute!
I can do it!
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
Are we done?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
It's over.
I've been doing this for a long time. I've only done this for a long time. Yes, let's go! Let's go! Yes!
Wrong. Well, let's go!
You made a mistake!
That was cute.
How did I get it wrong?
I made a mistake.
But it was cute. That's what I mean.
Before I raise my face, even if you don't, I won't do my best.
I'll do my best!
You're super cute!
Yes, OK!
Thank you very much!
Good luck!
This is crazy!
Awww...
I believe in you...you're so cute...you're so cute...you're so cute...you're so cute...you're so cute!
Hmmm...
Mmm...
Hm?
Mmm.
mmm
mmm...
I can do it! I can do it! Thank you! Bon appétit!
That was hard.
I closed my mouth when I was singing.
But I'll figure it out.
I don't know. Did I do it?
I'm not sure.
I can't wait to hear what you guys think!
I love summer.
I'm so cute ok, I'm done! Yay! I'm a little nervous!
I'm anxious, but so many people told me how cute I am.
I'm so excited!
I'm glad.
I tried my best to make it cute.
Please put a cute filter on your head!
Well, I'm off to lunch!
4 seconds.
Thank you very much.
Please let it rain!
I have to have it!
I think it's cute, isn't it?
I did my best.
It was cold.
So many!
I thought there weren't any, but there are some noisy ones.
Really?
I'm cold!
Some people are loud!
You're so cute! He's real! Oh, Mr. Gargle, Mr. Gargle is here! So cute!
It's real!
Real, real, real, real, real!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
They have food!
I hear you, I hear you!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Hey, if you're a little more full,
I wish you would've made me eat, I would've!
Oh, wait! Yum!
You know, if the camera's rolling, we'll look like ants, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah! There are, aren't there? Oh, yes!Oh, oh, yes! You have it, don't you? Oh, yes!
I'm going to eat it!
Ganbaru!
Go comment on YouTube and tell me how many minutes and seconds Norimaru is cute!
I promise!
Today we are having a dinner party with all the Candy Tune members!
Yay! Well, I can't eat, but I can't eat! It's a dinner party with all the Candy Tunes! Yay!
Well, I can't eat.
I can't eat.
It's okay to eat around here.
Let's eat!
Yes!
Good morning!
Cute!
Is this food?
It's food.
Hey, Ri-chan, isn't it cute? How do you like it? You're so picky.
It's good.
Can I have some bread?
Go ahead.
Bread, sir.
Looks delicious.
Aren't you going to the end of the line?
I'm not going to the edge at all.
Ehhhh...
Ohhh...
That's not fair.
I'm totally waiting.
My ears are all red.
I can't talk!
Oh, my God.
We're cutting.
Okay, that's fine.
I'll fix your makeup.
Make sure there's no bread on it.
Check.
Okay. - Okay.
I can't see.
You're so cute.
so cute so cute so cute
Thank you for the pink!
The kids were walking barefoot.
I don't get it.
Isn't it strong? I don't get it.
If we played shiritori now, I'm sure I'd lose.
Oh, Rubian.
Hey, Rubian.
Why don't you let me play Shiritori?
Cat.
Koko.
Komachan.
You lost, you're the one who lost.
Who are you, Komachan.
That's all. From this side
Arrah! Arrah!
Yes, I'm off.
The shooting is over, where I have a lot of things to say that I want to be praised! We are Aulakh! Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
Thank you, Osaka!
Thank you so much!
So, we finished shooting Hanemaru's music video!
Yay!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work! Thank you very much. Thank you so much.
So, we finished shooting Hanamaru's music video. Yay!
How was it?
It was fun.
It's cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
That was a lot of fun.
Which one?
You want to go?
Vicnic?
Is that good?
If we eat a lot of good food. Suddenly it's like all-you-can-eat.
Ayaji was too enthusiastic and got angry with me.
I got too carried away and got angry,
Please pay attention.
I hope you will rewind and watch it again.
I would be happy if you could rewind and watch the music video as well,
I would be happy if you could check out the music video as well.
Also, please love the music of Hana Girls.
Please do.
Please continue to support Candy14.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
bye bye.